checksure.biz 2017-05-23

# Privacy Policy

We have created this Privacy Policy ("Policy") to demonstrate our commitment to the privacy of your personal information. The following sets out our information-gathering and dissemination practices for this website.

If you have any questions or queries regarding this policy, please contact our Privacy Officer at checkSURE Customer Services. We will do our best to deal with your questions or queries as soon as possible.

**Privacy legislation**

Checksure Limited ("checkSURE") is subject to European and UK privacy legislation in the form of the Data Protection Act 1998, which regulates the use of individuals' personal information. This legislation imposes specific requirements on checkSURE and ensures that your personal information will only be used in accordance with this Policy.

**Data use**

We will not normally ask visitors to this website to reveal any personal information. However, we will collect some data about visitors including but not limited to IP addresses and details of the web browser and domain name each visitor uses. 

We will ask visitors who register with us ("Users") to supply us with personal data as defined in the Data Protection Act 1998 including but not limited to names, contact details and payment details.

checkSURE does not gather any more information about Users without their knowledge and active participation and permission than as is set out in this Policy.

You agree that we may use your personal information supplied via this website to keep you informed of any activities undertaken by checkSURE or its Associates and Subsidiaries (together "the Checksure Group") and other relevant companies which we believe may be of interest to you.

Part of our use of your personal information may include sending you e-mail messages. If you do not wish to receive messages please notify us by e-mail at the address at the end of this Policy.

checkSURE and the Checksure Group may use all personal information collected via the website.

You agree that we may disclose your personal information amongst members of the Checksure Group and other suitable third parties to allow the performance of services we provide to you or procure on your behalf or to further the reasonable commercial ends of the Checksure Group. Any such disclosure will be in accordance with checkSURE's responsibilities as a Data Controller under the Data Protection Act 1998.

**Cookies**

We sometimes use an Internet device called a cookie to store login or other information on your computer. A cookie is a small piece of information stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies are used to make the link between you and the information you have provided to the website, to identify users and personalise their visit by customising web pages for them. Most websites automatically accept cookies although you do not have to. If you disable cookies from your browser, you may not be able to access certain features of our website.

For certain services, we will allow you to have an ID or password stored in a cookie. We do not store payment details in cookies. 

_View Cookie Policy_

**Security of personal information**

We recognise the need to ensure that personal information gathered via this website remains secure. Our site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the personal information under our control.

You acknowledge that although we exercise adequate care and security there remains a risk that information transmitted over the Internet and stored by computer may be intercepted or accessed by an unauthorised third party.

**Transmission of personal information**

You agree that the Checksure Group may legitimately transfer your personal information to third parties located outside of the European Economic Area. In the event the checkSURE is sold or integrated with another business, you agree that we may disclose your personal information to our advisers and any prospective purchasers and to our successor business.

**Legal disclosure**

In some cases we may be required to disclose your personal information to comply with legal requirements.

**Changes and Information**

Should you wish to have your information updated or corrected, you may either access and correct your Internet registration record online. Alternatively, you may contact _checkSURE Customer Service._

**Updates to Privacy Policy**

We may update this Policy at any time without notice. Updates will be marked with a new edition number and dated accordingly. You agree to be bound by the Policy then in force as it appears on our website.
